<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Jagwe</string>
    <string-array name="title_book">
        <item>The Truth</item>
        <item>Its Hard To Pretend</item>
        <item>My Peace Is You</item>
        <item>Parallel Universe </item>
        <item>Yun To Roz Aati Hai</item>
        <item>Men</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="detail_book">
        <item>The truth is that no matter how much you feel for someone it wont matter
            if you can  t express those feelings of yours in front of that person.
            It doesnt mean that your feelings are useless but its just that it would be
            of no use or make no sense if the concerned person doesnt have
            any idea about it. Yaa, I get it that one should understand it even if its clearly
            said but for that also you  will have to start expressing it either through
            the words or through the actions. You know? Sometimes, one knows about
            the other persons feelings but he/she needs to be assured that
            whatever he/she is thinking is true or not. And that can only happen
            once the first person starts expressing it.
            So yaa, if you are feeling something then dont be afraid
            to express it💓
            #jagwe</item>
        <item>Its there. I can still feel it.
            I know that I  have been trying to pretend that its long gone
            but I dont know its still there. Turns out, Its not that easy
            to let go of something that once was the treasure of your life.
            I didnt know that whether it is was perfect or not?
            Because to me it never really mattered.
            All the time when I was there having it,
            I was busy hiding it from all the things that
            could  ve possibly taken it away.
            But I guess I  am not that good at keeping things
            a secret especially the ones which are so precious.
            Since then I  am trying to let it go and live the truth
            but it seems like my truth is just another lie.
            I think it  s gone but in reality, it  s still there.
            I  am just making fool of myself while pretending that its not there.
            Because It is. And it will always be.
            No matter what happens❤
            #jagwe</item>
        <item> Because for me, Peace is you💘 I dont have to look for both of you differently.
            Because I know that I will find peace once I found you.
            I dont know if I  am looking at the right place or not?
            I dont know if I  will find any of it or not. I dont know if
            I  ve enough time to keep looking or not. I don  t know anything.
            But all I can think of right now is that what it would be like to
            actually find you and hold you in arms and rest my head in your arms.
            I don  t care how much time it takes,
            I know that once Ido it will be all worth it.
            Because for me,Peace is you💘.
            #jagwe</item>
        <item>
            Right now sitting under this dark and beautiful sky.
            Holding each other. Loving each other.
            Planning our future and by future,
            I dont mean the next 10-12 years from now.
            By future I mean what we are going to do
            for the rest of the night🥺❤️
            This is what I wanted to do with you in the life
            but it  s okay.
            I hope that somewhere in a parallel universe,
            Maybe we are still together💘
            #jagwe </item>
        <item>
Yun to roz aati hai,
lekin aaj kuch jyada aa rahi hai.
Ye yaadein hi to hai jo mujhe roz
til til maar rahi hai.
Aisa nahi hai ke
mai kuch kar nahi sakta inke
baare me,
Mai chahu to bhula du inko.
Mai chahu to mita du inko.
lekin ye uske ishq ka asar hai
jo mere dil ko uski nishani maankar
inhe salamat rakhne ke liye
mana rahi hai.
Kuch sawaal hai jo mere hai lekin
mujhse nahi hai.
Kyu aur kaise se meri naraazgi hai.
Kyu aaj me mai kal me jee raha hu?
Kyu kal me mai bas us pal jee raha hu?
Kyu ye swaalo ke ghere hai?
Kyu mere din me raat se andhere hai?
Kyu se mai kyu bhaag raha hu?
Sara jahan sogya hai sirf
mai akela kyu jaag raha hu?
.
Maine khudse puche aise kayi sawaal hai.
Jinka jawaab milna abhi baaki hai.
Jawaab se vaise to koi raabta nahi mujhe,
lekin waqt ki kami thodi sata rahi hai.
Jee to aaj bhi raha hu mai
thoda- thoda
lekin meri saansein to ye
yaadein liye jaa rahi hai.
Yun to roz aati hai lekin aaj
kuch jyada aa rahi hai.

        </item>
        <item>
            Men.
Good or bad?
You decide.
I know some of them have hurt you in a way you never imagined but when one man was doing bad deeds another man who is your father/son/brother/boyfriend/husband/friend was there for you, with you, and was ready to fight for you.
Every gender has some bad people.
That doesnt make the whole gender a disgrace.
Does it?
.
Its not a secret that Men are not perfect at all.
They are full of flaws, no doubt.
But you will have to agree with me on this that despite all those flaws and imperfections they do try to make their loved ones happy and dedicate their whole life to them.
.
Everyone deserves to be loved and cared for.
And if someone does something wrong then he/she
deserves to be punished too.
But no one deserves to be judged based on another
persons doings.
.
People say a lot of things like
Be a man, Man up, Don  t be a coward,
Have some balls, Men dont have feelings,
All men are the same, Men are dogs, etc…
But the thing is that its hard to fight when
the majority is on the other side.
.
So, Love the Man/Men that you have in your life right now,
Who have stood by your side in good and bad times.
Love them or Not. Its upon you.
Just dont Hate them because of others.
️
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>